<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><recordset total="6"><record><cms_id><![CDATA[261]]></cms_id><cms_heading><![CDATA[Welcome]]></cms_heading><cms_content><![CDATA[<p></p>]]></cms_content><cms_image1><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1><cms_image1_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1_alt><cms_image2><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2><cms_image2_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2_alt><cms_cat><![CDATA[6]]></cms_cat><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish><sort_order><![CDATA[1]]></sort_order><advertising><![CDATA[]]></advertising><speaker1_name><![CDATA[Paul Tilstone]]></speaker1_name><speaker1_desc><![CDATA[Paul started his career in travel management company (TMC) sales & marketing roles for the business travel sector in 1993.  In 2005 he took up the post of CEO for the UK & Ireland’s Institute of Travel & Meetings (ITM) where he developed research, sustainability projects and industry affairs.  He then launched the Global Business Travel Association (GBTA) in Europe in 2010, moving to SVP Global Development in 2012 with a brief to develop GBTA regions outside of the USA.  In 2013, he also became deputy editor of Global Business Travel magazine.



In 2015 he launched consultancy Festive Road, www.festive-road.com and is a non-Executive Director of Xenia, an Italian based hotel technology company. 



He has been listed in the UK’s Buying Business Travel Hotlist and twice listed as one of the world’s top 25 business travel industry influencers by the Business Travel News, USA, for work in advocacy and sustainability.



Paul is based in Surrey in the UK.

]]></speaker1_desc><speaker1_img><![CDATA[PT_on_stage_2_2.jpg]]></speaker1_img><speaker2_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_name><speaker2_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_desc><speaker2_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_img><speaker3_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_name><speaker3_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_desc><speaker3_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_img><date_time><![CDATA[3]]></date_time><time><![CDATA[11:00 - 11:10]]></time><schedule_title_id><![CDATA[3]]></schedule_title_id><schedule_date><![CDATA[2016-04-17]]></schedule_date><schedule_title><![CDATA[Day 2]]></schedule_title><friendly_date><![CDATA[Sunday 17th April]]></friendly_date><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish></record><record><cms_id><![CDATA[237]]></cms_id><cms_heading><![CDATA[The Buyer’s Perspective: Progress]]></cms_heading><cms_content><![CDATA[<p>As travel management companies continue to develop their

role, our featured speaker presents research that supports the importance that

a TMC really plays in the life of a managed travel programme. We explore six

key areas where travel agencies need to keep a watchful eye and how they can

work closer with their clients to create the perfect partnership.</p>

<p></p>]]></cms_content><cms_image1><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1><cms_image1_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1_alt><cms_image2><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2><cms_image2_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2_alt><cms_cat><![CDATA[6]]></cms_cat><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish><sort_order><![CDATA[2]]></sort_order><advertising><![CDATA[n]]></advertising><speaker1_name><![CDATA[Simone Buckley CEO - ITM]]></speaker1_name><speaker1_desc><![CDATA[Simone joined ITM as Chief Executive Officer in January 2012 with responsibility for the commercial and strategic success of the association. The ITM represents more than 3000 buyer and supplier members from the travel industry and is the UK partner of GBTA.



Previously Simone held the position of Managing Director at Capita Business Travel where she was responsible for the strategy, sales and overall management of the company targeting both the public and private sector. During this time she was appointed onto the Executive Board of the GTMC where she chaired the Surface Transport Working Party and worked diligently with her peers on leading industry initiatives. 



Simone has both national and global experience previously holding senior positions at Carlson Wagonlit Travel, Rosenbluth International and HRG.

]]></speaker1_desc><speaker1_img><![CDATA[Simone_Buckley_-_high_res.png]]></speaker1_img><speaker2_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_name><speaker2_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_desc><speaker2_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_img><speaker3_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_name><speaker3_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_desc><speaker3_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_img><date_time><![CDATA[3]]></date_time><time><![CDATA[11:10 - 11:40]]></time><schedule_title_id><![CDATA[3]]></schedule_title_id><schedule_date><![CDATA[2016-04-17]]></schedule_date><schedule_title><![CDATA[Day 2]]></schedule_title><friendly_date><![CDATA[Sunday 17th April]]></friendly_date><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish></record><record><cms_id><![CDATA[238]]></cms_id><cms_heading><![CDATA[In the Hot Seat: Buyer Insights]]></cms_heading><cms_content><![CDATA[<p>Listen as Buyers present deeper insights into six key areas

that mark the cornerstone of a successful corporate travel programme and TMC

relationship.</p>

<p></p>

<p></p>

<ul>

 <li>Fare search &amp; ticketing</li>

 <li>Risk &amp; security</li>

 <li>Policy &amp; compliance</li>

 <li>Data &amp; analytics</li>

 <li>Settlement &amp; payment</li>

 <li>Consulting &amp; added value services</li>

</ul>

<p>Panellists: Jenni Joynt, Hilti | Nicky Rogan, Symantec | Kerrie Hudson, YBS Group</p>

<p></p>

<p></p>

<p></p>

<p></p>

<p></p>

<p></p>]]></cms_content><cms_image1><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1><cms_image1_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1_alt><cms_image2><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2><cms_image2_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2_alt><cms_cat><![CDATA[6]]></cms_cat><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish><sort_order><![CDATA[3]]></sort_order><advertising><![CDATA[n]]></advertising><speaker1_name><![CDATA[Caroline Strachan Managing Partner - Festive Road]]></speaker1_name><speaker1_desc><![CDATA[Caroline has worked in the travel and meetings industry for 20+ years. She has held roles as both buyer and supplier, so brings a unique perspective across the whole travel supply chain. Most recently Caroline led the Global Consulting group at American Express, helping a broad customer base tackle complex travel programme/industry issues. Prior to this Caroline led the AstraZeneca Global Travel Programme and was awarded the Best Travel Team category in the 2013 Business Travel Awards. 



Caroline has also led travel programmes at Yahoo and Cisco and sat on the Global Business Travel Association (GBTA) Board of Directors, chaired GBTA in Europe and the Institute of Travel Management (ITM) in the UK. Caroline has received a number of industry awards including the GBTA Luoma award in 2012 for services to the European travel and meetings industry and the Business Travel News Multinational Travel Manager of the Year award in 2013. Caroline is often called “the most credible Business Travel expert” in the industry, further supported by being published as one of three “industry influencers” in the Buying Business Travel 2016 Hotlist.

]]></speaker1_desc><speaker1_img><![CDATA[Caroline_Strachan.jpg]]></speaker1_img><speaker2_name><![CDATA[Nikki Rogan Global Travel Manager - Symantec Corporation]]></speaker2_name><speaker2_desc><![CDATA[Nikki Rogan is the Global Travel Manager for Symantec Corporation, the global leader in cybersecurity.



Nikki is responsible for the strategic management of the global travel programme in 35 countries.  This includes the management of the overall programme and policy, supplier relationship management, process efficiency, driving savings, customer experience, mitigating risk and managing an internal team.



Nikki has been in the business travel industry for the last 16 years, starting her career with travel management companies CWT and HRG prior to joining Symantec Corporation in 2006.

]]></speaker2_desc><speaker2_img><![CDATA[Nikki_Rogan.JPG]]></speaker2_img><speaker3_name><![CDATA[Jenni Joynt Travel Business Partner - Hilti (Gt. Britain) Ltd]]></speaker3_name><speaker3_desc><![CDATA[Jenni started her travel career working for British Airways at 18, and stayed with the company for 5 years, before pursuing a short career in HR.  In 2011 Jenni moved to Dubai to work for Emirates as Cabin Crew.  When the opportunity arose to become a travel buyer within the construction industry Jenni moved back to England to develop herself and the role as Travel Business Partner for Hilti GB.  Jenni works within a procurement team where she is responsible for Travel category spend, Strategic Meetings Management and Capital Equipment for their Distribution Centre. Jenni is in her final year of studying for her full CIPs qualification which she has successfully progressed through over the past three years.]]></speaker3_desc><speaker3_img><![CDATA[Joynt_Jennifer.jpg]]></speaker3_img><date_time><![CDATA[3]]></date_time><time><![CDATA[11:40 - 12:30]]></time><schedule_title_id><![CDATA[3]]></schedule_title_id><schedule_date><![CDATA[2016-04-17]]></schedule_date><schedule_title><![CDATA[Day 2]]></schedule_title><friendly_date><![CDATA[Sunday 17th April]]></friendly_date><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish></record><record><cms_id><![CDATA[239]]></cms_id><cms_heading><![CDATA[The Perfect TMC: Facing the Challenges]]></cms_heading><cms_content><![CDATA[<p>Hear perspective and insight on the TMC by those that know them intimately well, as reflections are drawn on what the buyers have said and what else is coming round the corner.</p>

<p>Panellists: Ken McLeod, Advantage | Colin Goldney, Aria Management</p>

<p></p>]]></cms_content><cms_image1><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1><cms_image1_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1_alt><cms_image2><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2><cms_image2_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2_alt><cms_cat><![CDATA[6]]></cms_cat><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish><sort_order><![CDATA[4]]></sort_order><advertising><![CDATA[n]]></advertising><speaker1_name><![CDATA[Ken McLeod Corporate Director - Advantage Travel Partnership ]]></speaker1_name><speaker1_desc><![CDATA[Ken McLeod has over 40 years' experience in the travel industry. He joined Advantage in July 2004 and is Corporate Director, with responsibility for airline relationships and business travel and serves on the Board.





McLeod began his career at the former Scottish multiple travel agent AT Mays, which grew to over 400 locations throughout the UK. He then moved on to become Director of Operations for an Icelandic tour company for three years, before returning to AT Mays, as Director and General Manager, to start up a new fare consolidation unit called Airsavers. In the following 11 years, the division grew from three employees into a call centre with over 80 staff and a turnover of £65 million. When AT Mays was acquired by the Carlson Group, McLeod was promoted to Head of Product and Planning for the leisure division for two years before moving on to become Managing Director of Canadian Affair, and subsequently introducing American Affair into the market.

In 1999 the US-based consortium, Travelsavers International, appointed McLeod as MD UK and Europe. The company’s eventual centralisation of European operations to Shannon, Ireland in 2003 provided the opportunity to join Advantage. 

McLeod is currently an active member of the AAC (Association of ATOL Companies), Vice President of the SPAA (Scottish Passenger Agents Association) and sits on the Virgin Atlantic TMC Advisory Board and the ATOC (Association of Train Operating Companies) Industry Advisory Committee in addition to serving on  IATA’s NDC Steering Committee for two years.

]]></speaker1_desc><speaker1_img><![CDATA[Ken_McLeod.jpg]]></speaker1_img><speaker2_name><![CDATA[Colin Goldney]]></speaker2_name><speaker2_desc><![CDATA[Having worked previously for The Bank of England and then Shell Oil, Colin entered UK travel in 1997 as the Head of European Marketing, Corporate Travel, American Express. In 2003 Colin was a founder member of Argate Meridian (a small London based Business Management consultancy) and has advised many of the world's major airlines, GDS, hotels and rail operators on their TMC and leisure agent distribution strategies across EMEA, N.America, India and Far East. 

Colin now works primarily within the growing business mergers, company acquisitions and company disposals practice (with representation on both the buyer and vendor side). He has advised on the sourcing and completion of 4 successful TMC/Leisure Agent acquisitions over the last 20 months - both trade sales and equity investment backed. Colin lives in West London.

]]></speaker2_desc><speaker2_img><![CDATA[Colin_Goldney_1.jpg]]></speaker2_img><speaker3_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_name><speaker3_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_desc><speaker3_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_img><date_time><![CDATA[3]]></date_time><time><![CDATA[12:30 - 13:00]]></time><schedule_title_id><![CDATA[3]]></schedule_title_id><schedule_date><![CDATA[2016-04-17]]></schedule_date><schedule_title><![CDATA[Day 2]]></schedule_title><friendly_date><![CDATA[Sunday 17th April]]></friendly_date><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish></record><record><cms_id><![CDATA[240]]></cms_id><cms_heading><![CDATA[The Missing Link: Have we got (Business Travel) news for you]]></cms_heading><cms_content><![CDATA[<p>Watch as we recreate a popular comedy quiz show that puts

Suppliers in the hot seat and grills them on the industry&rsquo;s top topics.</p>

<p></p>]]></cms_content><cms_image1><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1><cms_image1_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1_alt><cms_image2><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2><cms_image2_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2_alt><cms_cat><![CDATA[6]]></cms_cat><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish><sort_order><![CDATA[5]]></sort_order><advertising><![CDATA[n]]></advertising><speaker1_name><![CDATA[David Clare Publisher, The Business Travel Magazine]]></speaker1_name><speaker1_desc><![CDATA[Dave has been involved in the travel industry for over 20 years. During this time he has launched two leading titles and established numerous industry events.  His most recent publication The Business Travel Magazine has collected numerous awards and has created the springboard for the organisation of events including The People Awards, The Golf Masters, TBTM Christmas Party, The Business Travel Conference and the recently launched Dinner Club.

When not hard at work Dave can normally been found on the golf course or walking his dog - in fact he’ll do anything to avoid DIY as there are only so many times he can drill through water pipes or electric cables.



Dave has also graced TV screens with appearances on Who Wants to be Millionaire with the coughing major and more recently Tipping Point.  He had an all but too short career as a model (yes honestly) with appearances in My Guy, Photo Secret Love and The Grange Hill Annual 1986.



It’s fair to say that Dave enjoys life to the full and is never happier than when having a beer in his hand and enjoying the company of his industry colleagues.

]]></speaker1_desc><speaker1_img><![CDATA[Dave_Claire_1.jpg]]></speaker1_img><speaker2_name><![CDATA[Jackie Clarke, British Airways]]></speaker2_name><speaker2_desc><![CDATA[Jackie Clark is the Manager for TMC Partnerships in UK&I for British Airways and Iberia. 



Jackie has 18 years of experience within BA.  She has worked in a number of roles within the sales organisation in all channels culminating in her current role of heading up the TMC channel overseeing commercial and trade body relationships that BA have with the UK TMC market. 



Previously, Jackie held the position of Managing Director of Call BA, a wholly owned subsidiary of BA.  Based in Delhi, this call centre delivered operational support for 9 global markets, as well as overseeing the Hong Kong operation covering China, Hong Kong and Japan.



Jackie lives in Amersham and has a keen interest in good wine, socialising and not surprisingly travel!

]]></speaker2_desc><speaker2_img><![CDATA[Jackie_Clark_BAto_use.jpg]]></speaker2_img><speaker3_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_name><speaker3_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_desc><speaker3_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_img><date_time><![CDATA[5]]></date_time><time><![CDATA[08:30 - 09:30]]></time><schedule_title_id><![CDATA[5]]></schedule_title_id><schedule_date><![CDATA[2016-04-19]]></schedule_date><schedule_title><![CDATA[Day 4]]></schedule_title><friendly_date><![CDATA[Tuesday 19th April]]></friendly_date><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish></record><record><cms_id><![CDATA[241]]></cms_id><cms_heading><![CDATA[Creating the Vision]]></cms_heading><cms_content><![CDATA[<p>Have your say in this interactive breakout session as you

get the opportunity to discuss your perspectives &ndash; and hear those of your peers

&ndash; on the key topics of the day. What are the priorities for a successful future

TMC and can we develop a template for success &ndash; you will decide!</p>

<p></p>]]></cms_content><cms_image1><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1><cms_image1_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image1_alt><cms_image2><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2><cms_image2_alt><![CDATA[]]></cms_image2_alt><cms_cat><![CDATA[6]]></cms_cat><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish><sort_order><![CDATA[6]]></sort_order><advertising><![CDATA[n]]></advertising><speaker1_name><![CDATA[Paul Tilstone, Festive Road]]></speaker1_name><speaker1_desc><![CDATA[Paul started his career in travel management company (TMC) sales & marketing roles for the business travel sector in 1993.  In 2005 he took up the post of CEO for the UK & Ireland’s Institute of Travel & Meetings (ITM) where he developed research, sustainability projects and industry affairs.  He then launched the Global Business Travel Association (GBTA) in Europe in 2010, moving to SVP Global Development in 2012 with a brief to develop GBTA regions outside of the USA.  In 2013, he also became deputy editor of Global Business Travel magazine.



In 2015 he launched consultancy Festive Road, www.festive-road.com and is a non-Executive Director of Xenia, an Italian based hotel technology company. 



He has been listed in the UK’s Buying Business Travel Hotlist and twice listed as one of the world’s top 25 business travel industry influencers by the Business Travel News, USA, for work in advocacy and sustainability.



Paul is based in Surrey in the UK.

]]></speaker1_desc><speaker1_img><![CDATA[PT_on_stage_2.jpg]]></speaker1_img><speaker2_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_name><speaker2_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_desc><speaker2_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker2_img><speaker3_name><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_name><speaker3_desc><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_desc><speaker3_img><![CDATA[]]></speaker3_img><date_time><![CDATA[5]]></date_time><time><![CDATA[09:30 - 10:30]]></time><schedule_title_id><![CDATA[5]]></schedule_title_id><schedule_date><![CDATA[2016-04-19]]></schedule_date><schedule_title><![CDATA[Day 4]]></schedule_title><friendly_date><![CDATA[Tuesday 19th April]]></friendly_date><publish><![CDATA[y]]></publish></record></recordset>